<resources>
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="app_name">CVapp</string>
    <string name="emailInfo">Email:\n<u>whiskers@purrmail.com</u></string>
    <string name="email">whiskers@purrmail.com</string>
    <string name="phoneInfo">Phone:\n<u>(555) MEOW-123</u></string>
    <string name="phoneNumber">+380663944780</string>
    <string name="shortInfo">I\'m a motivated and enthusiastic individual with a strong interest in the logistics industry.
        At present, I\'m in my third year of studying for a bachelor\'s degree in logistics at ABC University.
        I have outstanding communication skills and can communicate effectively with a wide range of people.
        I\'m looking for a part-time position to utilise my knowledge and experience.
    </string>
    <string name="back_arrow">⇦</string>
    <string name="title_activity_big_photo">BigPhoto</string>
    <string name="more_info">
<b>Whiskers the Cat</b>

\n123 Feline Lane | Kittyville, USA | (555) MEOW-123 | whiskers@purrmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/whiskersthecat

\n<b>Objective:</b>
\nA charismatic and agile feline seeking a loving home where I can showcase my purr-fect personality and bring joy to my human companions. With a proven track record of lap-warming, mouse-hunting, and laser-chasing, I am ready to contribute my unparalleled expertise in napping and entertaining.

\n<b>Education:</b>

        \n<u>Purradise Kitty Academy | Kittyville, USA | Graduated: May 2021</u>

\n•Specialization in Napping 101 and Advanced Purring Techniques.
\n•Top of the class in Playful Paw Movements and Laser Dot Navigation.

\n<b>Work Experience:</b>

        \n<u>Chief Lap Warmer | Whisker\'s Haven, Kittyville, USA | Jan 2021 - Present</u>

\n•Expertly warmed laps during chilly evenings, ensuring maximum comfort for humans.
\n•Conducted strategic nap sessions to boost productivity and morale in the household.
\n•Engaged in daily grooming sessions, maintaining a silky and luxurious coat.
        \n<u>Mouse Hunter | Furry Critter Exterminators, Kittyville, USA | June 2020 - Dec 2020</u>

\n•Successfully apprehended and neutralized pesky mouse invaders, earning the title of "Top Hunter" for three consecutive months.
\n•Collaborated with the household security team to implement effective mouse prevention strategies.
        \n<u>Toy Tester | Purrfection Playthings Inc., Kittyville, USA | Jan 2019 - May 2020</u>

\n•Participated in rigorous testing of catnip-infused toys, providing valuable feedback on durability, entertainment value, and overall fun factor.
\n•Developed a reputation for selecting the purr-fect toys that resonate with feline preferences.

\n<b>Skills:</b>

\n<u>Purring:</u>

\n•Advanced purring techniques, including the soothing purr, the content purr, and the attention-seeking purr.
        \n<u>Napping:</u>

\n•Strategic napping in sunbeams, cozy beds, and human laps.
\n•Proficient in the art of the "cat loaf" position for maximum relaxation.
        \n<u>Playfulness:</u>

\n•Adept at playful antics, including laser chasing, feather catching, and spontaneous zoomies.
\n<u>Communication:</u>

\n•Fluent in meows, chirps, and trills to effectively communicate needs and desires.
\n<u>Grooming:</u>

\n•Self-grooming expertise, maintaining a pristine and elegant appearance.
\n•Skilled in receiving human-assisted brushings for that extra touch of glamour.

\n<b>Certifications:</b>

    \n<u>Certified Catnip Connoisseur | International Catnip Association | June 2022</u>

\n•Recognized for exceptional discernment in identifying high-quality catnip.
    \n<u>Master Purrer | Feline Harmony Institute | August 2021</u>

\n•Completed an intensive course in advanced purring techniques, achieving the highest level of mastery.

\n<b>Hobbies and Interests:</b>

\n•Bird watching from the windowsill perch.
\n•Exploring the great indoors and discovering hidden nooks.
\n•Participating in impromptu staring contests with the resident goldfish.

\n<b>Volunteer Work:</b>

    \n<u>Therapy Cat | Paws for Comfort Foundation, Kittyville, USA | Ongoing</u>

\nSpread joy and comfort to humans in hospitals and nursing homes through therapeutic purring and cuddle sessions.

\n<b>References:</b>
\nAvailable upon request, preferably from humans with warm laps and a good supply of catnip-infused treats.</string>

</resources>